Go ahead, John.
>> What's up, Rashad? Congrats. Welcome to
Washington. Um, so I hear you know a
little bit about the quarterback. What's
it like for you to be reunited with
Jaden?
>> Uh, obviously it feel great. Uh, it's
like, you know, it's my best friend. Um,
you know, I know a lot about him. I
mean, whatever y'all want to know, I
give y'all all the secrets. But yeah, we
spent a lot of time together. Obviously
did a lot of things together and we
still do. always kept and talked a lot
almost every day since even you know
when he was back in college and I came
to the league. So you know it's grateful
I'm grateful to get an opportunity to
play here obviously and uh you know
fresh start.
>> So and you came in the league at a first
couple years and they they bring a
bucket you had to handle that. What did
you learn about yourself these last
couple of years that can help you going
forward?
Uh, I mean the biggest thing is, uh, the
way the league was trending. Uh, it was
trending. Yeah. When I came in, it
wasn't really big two backs. It was
still, you know, one back. Uh, you know,
with a spell and things like that, but
obviously the league been trending
towards two backs. And, you know,
obviously me and Bucky, we had our duo.
We had, we both did our thing. And, uh,
I think the biggest thing, obviously,
I'm coming to a situation where I know,
uh, too. Obviously, I know I'm pretty
I'm going to get asked this, but Bill
and things like that. So, it's a great
situation. Obviously, you know, um we
kept each other fresh over in Tampa. I'm
pretty sure Bill and I, we know we going
to do the same thing here. So, you know,
it's just a grateful situation.
Obviously, we competed and you learned a
lot about yourself, but I'm happy about
about a new start.
>> Thank you,
>> Nikki.
>> Hi, Rashad. Um I believe you posted
something on Instagram back in January
maybe hinting that you might want to
play with Dayton. Was this sort of your
your first choice? Um, you know, knowing
that you could be leaving Tampa?
>> Um,
first choice. Uh,
I don't I can't really allude to if it
was my first choice, but obviously it
was one of my top choices uh to come to.
Uh, thought of course it'd be a good
situation. Obviously, I thought it'd be
great, yeah, to play with like play with
my best friend again and things like
that. So, yeah, I mean, for sure it was
huge. But first choice, probably not.
But I'm glad, you know, where I'm at
now, I'm I'm happy with the decision
that I made and I'm glad they took a
chance on me and uh I'm grateful to be
here.
>> And just with your pass catching
ability, I mean, what do you bring to to
Washington? What do you what do you
think you can add to this offense?
>> Uh I think the biggest thing I bring is
a a competitor. Uh a guy that works
hard. Uh obviously I know uh last year
things didn't go as planned for for you
know the commanders as everybody wanted
it to especially coming off that the
other year. Um and so I think the
biggest thing for me I bring a a
different aspect of competing. Uh I'm a
dog obviously. I feel like I'm a running
back that can you know do everything. I
got a great uh skill set uh great feel
for the game and obviously you know uh
being in my fifth year now just uh a
certain presence to the running back
room I feel like I can uh give game and
drop jewels and you know help out uh the
younger guys you know that we gonna have
so it's it'll be huge.
>> David Aldridge
Dave, we can't hear you.
Try again.
Still nothing. We'll come back. Uh David
Harrison.
>> Hey Rashad, congratulations. Welcome to
DC. Um I know you've worked for you
played under, I should say, several
different offensive coordinators in your
career. What's something about David
Blau just from what you know right now
that kind of attracts you to to what he
might bring?
>> Uh I think the biggest thing is
obviously energy. Um his energy is
different. It's unique. Uh and I'm very
excited about that. Also, I think just
uh being able to play underneath uh
obviously a former player is huge. So I
know you know he sees the game
differently, especially at he was a
quarterback and you know uh he did his
thing. Um, and I said I think that's the
hugest thing, especially dropping
jewels. Uh, obviously like yeah, my best
friend is is the quarterback. So, you
know, obviously the OC being being a
former quarterback and things like that.
Obviously, it was appealing. And like I
said, just his brain. I know he's very
smart. I know he's very good and learned
a lot um throughout his career and
obviously throughout obviously his
coaching career so far, too. So, I just
thought it was a great, you know,
decision to come here. It was it it made
the most sense to me and you know happy
I'm here.
>> And I know in Tampa you were really good
about interacting with fans when you
have the opportunity to and you've
talked about the importance that fans
can bring on game day. What is your kind
of early impression of of the Commanders
fan base so far?
>> Uh yeah, obviously it's been huge. Uh
they've been showing a lot of love to me
obviously on social media and things
like that. Uh they kind of been doing
that for a while now and uh yeah,
obviously I'm really appreciative. I'm
really grateful. Uh obviously I know you
know what's expected of me and uh you
know from organization standpoint and
from fan standpoint and yeah I'm just
big on going out in the community giving
back just doing different things. So uh
they they'll see a lot of me and and it'
be huge. It's all love.
>> Thanks
>> David Aldridge. Do we have you?
>> I hope so. Y'all got me now?
>> Yeah.
>> There we go. All right. Hey Rashad,
welcome to DC man. Um hopefully you
weren't asked this while I was out, but
you uh excelled in pass pro um among
your other things. I just wonder how you
how you were challenged to become good
at that and what you did to become good
at that.
>> Um I just say some of the coaches that I
had along the way uh they was uh huge on
obviously being able to uh keep the
quarterback upright. you know, the
quarterback is the one that makes, you
know, uh, obviously the Boer a lot of
the money and, um, you know, protecting
him is huge and, uh, quarterback
obviously is essential to us winning
games. So, uh, it boils down to two,
just doing my job, uh, doing what I'm
asked to do. I mean, that's a part of my
job description. So, uh, I remember I
said this kind of when I was coming out
that I try to pride myself on being able
to do a lot of things and do a lot of
things well on the field and I feel like
my game and my skill set and my talent,
you know, shows that. So, I think
obviously it's important to pass protect
because that's my job and I need to do
it at a high level. So, that's what I
do. I take pride in that.
>> Um, I asked Leo Chanel the same thing
like um, you were in a good situ I mean
you're in a good team last year. You
know, Tampa's been good for a minute.
Um, you could have stayed there, you
could have gone somewhere else. I I know
the J I know Jaden being here is
important to you, but um, just wondering
like what got you to Yes. with a team
that's kind of on on the on the building
side as opposed to already being there.
>> Uh, I just think culture. Uh, yeah, you
know, rebuilding or things like that.
Obviously, it's kind of tough. You never
know how the season could have went last
year for Washington. I mean, you know,
we don't like to make, you know,
excuses. I always say the game ain't
based off of sympathy, so it ain't no
sympathy. But, as well as we got to be
real and realistic. And, uh, they had
obviously it was a lot of injuries last
year. Uh, Jaden obviously too had a lot
of injuries, but just the team in
general. So, you really never know what
could have shook out, but what happened
happened. Uh I think just all the other
pieces that's around. Uh I think uh the
offensive line just a lot of other good
things that like I think they already
kind of to me had in place um and what I
seen uh when I watched tape and and
looked over here and things like that of
where I feel like I could excel and I
could have an impact, you know, on on
the team. So uh this was huge. obviously
the opportunity and just like I said,
I'm thankful and grateful for this and
the opportunity here is huge and and
yeah, I'm for I'm for sure I'm grateful
for it and yeah, I'm ready to rock.
>> Thank you.
>> Hey Rashad, welcome to the DMV. So now
we know that we can find out the scoop
about Jaden, but what did Jaden tell you
about Washington and and being playing
for Washington since he's been here for
a while? What was the things that he
said stood out?
>> Uh, I think the biggest thing he told me
it was just a great city, obviously
great fan base. Uh, like obviously a
great culture of what they was building
here. Um, obviously he got close to a
Super Bowl his rookie year. Um, and I
think, you know, his biggest thing was
obviously he's trying to win one. Um and
so you know obviously his biggest thing
is you know trying to of course you know
help
fit the mold of of guys he feel like can
help win one. So I think that was the
biggest thing. I mean obviously after um
you know uh the news broke and things
like that and stuff. We talked and you
know that was his biggest thing of of
and he know that the type of guy I am,
the type of player I am, the type of
competitor I am and who I am and my
character. So he felt like I fit too as
well and and trying to win and you know
that's what I'm about. So
>> and and you talked about learning things
about yourself. What are the biggest
things that through all these processes
that you've learned about yourself?
>> Um I think my biggest thing I learned uh
for me and obviously my journey is
different from a lot of people.
Obviously I feel like a lot of these
situations I've been here before. I
wasn't you know the highest recruit. I
wasn't this. I mean, a lot of guys
probably can say this or a lot of guys
probably can't, but I'm just speaking on
from my aspect and not worried about
obviously the other guys, but so he just
know and I just know who I am. Uh,
underdog mentality. I always got a chip
on my shoulder and you know, I think
that's uh the mode of what this team is.
So, I feel like for me, I just um had to
reset and I had to get back to who I was
and who I am. And you know, I'm just
happy, like I said, to be in a a great
situation, a great opportunity, a new
place, uh, like I said, a great city,
um, great fan base and a team that's,
you know, ready to compete and see what
happens.
>> Thanks,
>> Ben.
>> Hey, Todd. Welcome to town. Um, you said
you got the Jaden secrets. Okay. What
What do you got?
>> Nah, I mean, we kind of we lying right
now. I ain't I can't tell none of that.
So, you know, not lie.
>> How about How about this? He fancies
himself a good basketball player. What's
his game?
>> Yeah, for sure. We who before and that's
my boy. So, of course, he got game. He
got game. He athlete. He obvious
obviously we know he not one of them
football players that just say he can,
you know, play basketball and he really
can't. Like he's an athlete. He can play
he can do a lot of things.
>> When when you first met him, obviously
he's developed as a quarterback and as a
person. what what have you kind of seen
as the biggest growth maybe from the
time that you kind of met him to where
he is now both as a player and a person?
>> Uh, I mean that's that's that's that's
that's
um that's a great question. I think
because it's like when I first met him
obviously when I got to ASU I mean yeah
I thought you know and I tell people all
the time I used to go on interviews and
tell people all the time obviously and I
played with some you know good
quarterbacks. I ain't going to say that.
Obviously some some great quarterbacks.
Obviously I play with the greatest all
the time. But obviously they asked me
who I thought was the best quarterback I
always play with. I would always say him
uh just on the aspect how talented he
was and what all he can do. So I think
the biggest growth I seen him u
obviously do as a man is just you know
he always been to me the same way. He
locked in focus on his game focus on his
craft. He worked very hard. Um, I say
the biggest thing is just too how how he
moved, man, and how more vocal he he has
gotten. Um, he wasn't when I first met
him, he wasn't obviously the most vocal
guy, more lead by example, things like
that. But now he vocal. Uh, you know, he
comes out of shell and things like that.
And, you know, I'm just proud of him. I
mean, I remember we, like I said, we
used to always talk, we always talk all
the time, literally. And I still got
messages of him. He was coming off that
bye-week at LSU, got hurt or something,
then had a bye-week and we was just
texting about how he was gonna go win a
Heisman. Literally, I got the messages
to this day at that exact time. And I
said, "Yeah, you is. Go do it." And like
we always just been there for one
another, things like that. So, he just,
you know, he just that dude and
obviously everybody sees it.
>> Thank you,
>> Leak.
>> Welcome, Rashad to DC.
>> Appreciate it. Uh, you know, when you
look ahead and you look at this offense,
obviously led by Jaden and Terry, uh,
you know, bringing in weapons like
yourself and Chick as far as a tight end
and, you know, you guys are, uh, also in
conversations at least, you know, from
afar, uh, with a a former ASU teammate
of yours, a wide receiver. So, you know,
when you look at what this offense
potentially could be, how great do you
think you guys can take that next step?
Uh obviously yeah we have a lot of
obviously talent and they already really
have some talent I would say uh like I
said so uh obviously it's just huge uh
you know take it uh day by day obviously
coaching them they game planning and
they putting in the system and things
like that obviously you excited about
that like I said with coach D blau and
you know the background he come from
obviously the Detroit and all the other
things and other coaches he's been
around that he's met. I'm pretty sure he
gonna have his own little spin on things
though. But, uh, you just excited, you
know, you try to add weapons, you try to
add the right people, you try to add the
right players, the right guys with the
right character and the right mode. And
I think that's what obviously Adam is
doing. Uh, so you excited to get with
the guys, you're excited to work with
the guys, and you're excited, like you
said, for it all to come together. I
mean, yeah, it's looking real good to
me.
And when you look at a a guy like Austin
Eckler, you know, who's played at a high
level for most of his career, um, and
some of the things that he did in
Washington when he was here, uh, you
know, catching the ball out the
backfield, that's something that you
clearly have excelled at, and I know
David Aldridge mentioned that to you
earlier, but how do you feel like you
can implement some of your game into
this offense as far as the explosive
plays?
>> Yeah. Uh, I think obviously that's a
huge thing. Um and uh yeah, some of the
things you know that um I see and uh I
know some of the things probably that
coach Dlau want to you know put in and
things like that. I've been yeah blessed
and and I've been great at being able
yes to be out in space and uh make
things shake and be able to catch the
ball or be able to do a lot of things in
a screen game to you know turn some some
some things and some turn nothings into
somethings and things like that. So I'm
pretty sure yeah that would be huge. Uh
yeah, like I said, I think in my overall
impact for me, I just want to come in,
like I said, uh be a dog, uh be a
competitor. Um obviously help out in any
way that needs to be helped out, but for
sure have an impact and yeah, make plays
when when when I'm it's time for me to
make plays. So that's my mindset and
that's what I'm on.
>> All right. Congratulations.
>> Appreciate you.
>> All right. Appreciate it, Rashad.
Thanks.
>> Thank you guys.
>> Thanks, Rashad. Yeah. Thanks.
Recording stopped.